Hey, little miss, are you alright?
——이봐, 꼬마 아가씨, 괜찮아?
Pleasure to meet you. Who... might you be?
처음 뵙겠습니다…. 실례지만, 누구세요?
Galaxy Ranger. I received a distress signal. This place really is the territory of Dr. Primitive's henchmen. It's as hard to find as those *Ninja Slang* bananas hidden in the woods.
갤럭시 레인저, 난 구조 신호를 받고 왔다. *닌자 레인저 비속어*, 이 원시 박사 녀석들은 숲에 숨겨진 바나나처럼 *닌자 레인저 비속어*같이 찾기 힘드네
Ninja Hero? Huh. It seems my trial has finally come to an end.
닌자 레인저요? 이제 소인의 시련이 끝난 모양이네요……
Trial? What kind of *Ninja Slang*... Another poor kid driven mad by those monkeys, *Ninja Slang*.
시련? 무슨 *닌자 레인저 비속어* 뚱딴지같은 소리야…. 원숭이 땜에 정신이 나갔나 *닌자 레인저 비속어*
The final trial of the Mappou Age... Destroy the matrix of Osaru's house and end the catastrophe.
말법일하의 종극•시련… 원숭이 통치자의 진법을 파괴하고, 이곳을 뒤덮은 재앙을 없애는 거죠……
Pray tell... Have I proven myself worthy of the title of "Ninja Hero"?
지금의 소인은… 「닌자 레인저」라고 불릴 자격이 있을까요?
*Ninja Slang*, no way... So that's why all those *Ninja Slang* in the lab are lying dead on the ground.
*닌자 레인저 비속어* 말도 안 돼…. 어째 실험실 *닌자 레인저 비속어*들이 다 뒤져있다 했어
Was it all your doing?
전부 너 혼자서 한 거야?
Ten years of suffering, one day of recognition...
십 년의 고행을 거쳐 하루아침에 칭호를 받게 되다니……
I have not let down Dazzling Ninjutsu... Master Kucha, I really wish you could witness this...
소인은 지금껏 요란•인법을 헛되게 한 적이 단 한 번도 없어요. 쿠차 대사님이 이 모습을 보셨다면 좋았을 텐데……
*Ninja Slang*, I get it now. This girl's infected with a memetic virus. *Ninja Slang*, most people would've turned into complete *Ninja Slang* by now, but she's still running around like nothing's wrong?
*닌자 레인저 비속어* 이제 알겠네. 이 아가씨 밈 바이러스에 감염된 거네. 근데 보통 사람이라면 벌써 *닌자 레인저 비속어*이 됐어야 하는데 왜 아직도 멀쩡하지?
Please, listen to me! You're in serious danger right now. If you don't get treated soon, your brain will eventually burst!
이봐, 내 말 잘 들어! 넌 지금 아주 위험한 상태야. 치료를 받지 않으면 머리가 터질 거라고!
Wait! Since I am now a ninja hero who can contend with evil ninjas...
잠시만요! 지금의 소인은 사악 닌자를 대적할 만한 닌자 레인저가 되었으니……
Might I... lend you a hand?
소인도 돕고 싶어요
*Ninja Slang*, you're asking me this now. Do you have a death wish?
*닌자 레인저 비속어*, 그게 지금 할 소리냐. 죽고 싶어?
You want to go on The Hunt? Know that this is a road of no return!
죽으면 복수도 못 하는데 「수렵」의 길을 걷겠다고? 이건 무를 수도 없어!
Great Lan above. Eradicating evil, till my last breath. My bow drawn, no turning back...
대란신이시여. 모든 악을 멸할 때까지 멈추지 않고, 활시위에 걸린 화살이 영영 돌아오지 않는다 해도……
...My heart shall remain unmoved.
…일심불란, 파사현정을 지키겠어요!
Whoever follows the way of the ninja is a ninja. I...
「인도」를 관철하는 자가… 바로 닌자 레인저죠! 소인은……
I've made my decision.
결정했어요